Inventory of the Broadside Case Collection, 1896 - 2004
Broadside Case Collection, 1896 - 2004
- Buildings - Plans
  - Power House Plans, Plan for Underground Electric Wire Conduits, Plan for Underground High Tension Service.
    - Untitled Drawings (2).
    - Drawing. Brine Pipe.
    - Drawing. Vert. Section Through Subway and Sub Basement.
    - Drawing of Filtering Chamber.
    - Drawing of Unknown Structure with Brine Pipe.
    - Drawing of Vertical Sections.
    - Drawing of Unknown Structure with Brine Pipe.
    - Drawing. Floor Plan of Unknown Structure (2).
    - Drawing. Floor Plan of Various Workshops.
    - Drawing. Preliminary Sketch of Power House and Shops. Basement.
    - Drawing. Layout of Unknown Structure.
    - Drawing. Floor Plan of Various Laboratories and Rooms.
    - Blueprints. Plan for Conduit System to put Electric Wires underground. Duplicate.
    - Blueprints. Project B Plans and Details.